<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Red River .NET User Group</title>
    <description>The Red River .NET User Group meets the third Wednesday of each month at the LSUS Technology Center.
</description>
    <link>http://www.rrdnug.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://www.rrdnug.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 12:42:39 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 12:42:39 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>December Meeting: Nerd Dinner</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In lieu of our normal meeting, we’ll be eating dinner at Marilynn’s Place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSVP on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1528757967367558/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2014 06:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/december/nerd-dinner/2014/12/01/nerd-dinner.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/december/nerd-dinner/2014/12/01/nerd-dinner.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>meeting</category>
        
        <category>december</category>
        
        <category>nerd-dinner</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>November Meeting: Introduction to F#</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Jeremy Abbott is a developer at Shreveport development shop, Praeses, where he works as a project architect, developer, and recruiter. His development and architecture focus is on writing rich, extensible, and maintainable web applications. He’s passionate about software as a profession, and advocates for continuous learning and training. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When not writing code Jeremy is a vocal community leader and advocates for more visibility and inclusion for marginalized groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Functional programming is not always intuitive to developers coming from an object oriented background. With languages like JavaScript dominating the web, an understanding of functional paradigms has increased relevance. This talk covers F# as a hybrid functional/OOP language that brings the terseness of functional programming to the .NET framework. C# will often be brought in to compare and contrast how the same problem can be solved in both languages. F# concepts such as type inference, pattern matching, function composition, partial application and precomputation will be discussed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSVP on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/872248179472488/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/november/f%23/2014/11/01/introduction-to-f%23.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/november/f%23/2014/11/01/introduction-to-f%23.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>meeting</category>
        
        <category>november</category>
        
        <category>f#</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>October Meeting: ASP.NET vNext</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Brian Sullivan is a principal consultant for Improving Enterprises in Dallas. He got his start in programming maintaining legacy mainframe applications in COBOL at a large trucking company, but quickly realized he needed to find a more productive environment in order to stay sane. He jumped at the opportunity to help transition some of those COBOL applications to .NET, and he hasn’t looked back since. He has been working with Microsoft technologies since the .NET 1.0 days, and is interested in introducing modern web development techniques to the clients he works with. Brian is recipient of the Microsoft MVP award in ASP.NET and a graduate of Harding University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Web development was a different game back in the early 2000s. Early versions of ASP.NET were aimed at Microsoft’s existing customer base, and even tried to hide the nature of the web from developers who weren’t ready for it. The platform has evolved steadily since the .NET Framework was released, but many of the technical decisions made early in ASP.NET’s life don’t make sense in the context of modern web development. By cutting loose some of the baggage from earlier versions, the ASP.NET team has been able to make sweeping changes to bring the framework in line with its lightweight, agile contemporaries. In this presentation, Brian will show how the next version of ASP.NET will be leaner, faster, and more flexible than the platform has ever been.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RSVP on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/events/1492183807699795/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 07:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/october/aspnet/vnext/2014/10/01/aspnet-vnext.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://www.rrdnug.com/meeting/october/aspnet/vnext/2014/10/01/aspnet-vnext.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>meeting</category>
        
        <category>october</category>
        
        <category>aspnet</category>
        
        <category>vnext</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
